[Music]
a this is Hightech news TV news IC
Lombard kick started the ride out to
safety rally in Chennai aims to raise
awareness about road safety measures ICI
I lomard organized a right to safety
rally under it CSR initiative in Chennai
Chief guest Mr P Kumar Deputy
Commissioner traffic police North
District Chennai along with iici Lombard
senior management team flagged off the
event which aims to raise awareness
about road safety measures among two-
wheeler owners with the children riding
as billion Riders around 500 plus kids
along with their parents from nearby
School participated in the rally and
were given isi mocked helmets and made
them aware of non othering to the basic
rule of safety and wearing a helmet I I
I Lombard adopted a two pronged strategy
one to bring out a behavioral change in
Parental and children about Road Safety
through customized direct contact
programs and secondly by Distributing
child specific Isa marked helmets to
Children since the inspection of the
program in September 2015 the company
has touched 6 lakhs live by creating
awareness for life saving road safety
rules and the need for motor insurance
from a formative age in an important
Milestone IC I lomard has distributed 2
lakh 97,000 plus isi mocked helmets to
children and aims to distribute 1.5 lakh
plus helmets this financial year across
India as per the irda guidelines IC I
lomard is committed to increase
Insurance awareness through such CSR
initiative and keeping the promises of
our brand ethos of niaya v i is lomard
has been in a Pioneer in the industry
and is the first large scale insurance
company in India to migrate its entire
core systems to cloud with a strong
focus on being digital ail it has
launched a r of tech driven Innovations
including the industry first face scan
on its signature insurance and wellness
app I take care with over 6.9 million
user downloads the company has W the
several in including in ET corporate
excellence awards golden peacock Awards
ICC Insurance Awards National CSR Awards
and etc for its various
initiatives want to know the latest
updated news please subscribe Hightech
news TV channel thank
you the I Lampard free helmet
distrib
insurance company
so
[Music]
helmet
traffic
RMS and
follow so Road
us